So before we cannot verify if our device has been ready started Microsoft Intune so
what we need to do is let me go to my start menu and then I'm going to actually
just enter CMD. So that is open command prompt. If I open the command prompt I'm
just going to enter the following TS reg CMD and then status. So what I want to
confirm is you know when we were registered when we actually configure the MDM
users scope you can see we have for example the MDM URL and also we have the
access token. You can see we have some information here which actually very
very potent which of course I still do not want to modify during our
configuration and if I go back again let me go to my to Microsoft Intune and
this actually of my device let me do a refresh this Azure Active Directory and
now you can now see that this C002 which of course this device we registered was
I thought with Victoria John and now you can see it says it's been managed by
Microsoft Intune and it's at all the fashion of Windows and if I go to device
Microsoft Intune let me do a refresh you can see how this moment is says is
we're managed by Intune it's corporate and it's actually compliant and you
can see the OS is Windows and this is the device we joined to Intune. So now
we have been able to actually configure and auto and roll other files using
Microsoft Intune. The other moment we're not seeing this other device which is the
Windows 11 probably because this I'm logged onto this device as an administrator
and if I go to my CMD let me just enter the following one why you can see
says I'm using actually kelvin.gencin so let's do the following and see as the
TPU updates false we call not false the policy on this device so that's the
policy we just applied should now be a false on this device and see if the
device will now appear in Intune. For mind you I would need to actually verify
if kelvin dot John's in how the right license to be able to have the right
right Microsoft Intune license sorry so that's if not he will not be able to
join this device to Intune. So if I go to my users profile you can see we
have kelvin John's in okay kelvin John's in and as the kelvin John's in
that was actually sync from our own premises and you can see it has a Microsoft
3C5 if five license which means the device should be able to join to Microsoft
Intune. So at this moment let me just wait and what I'll say no for that and after
some minutes we can now start seeing the device also first of all in Azure AD
that the C001 so let me do a refresh I'd go to take some some minutes for
this to actually start appearing. So after some time definitely you will now
see that as device the C001 will manage by Intune but we're going to take some
time cut another log log off from this device and then log on again to the device
which of course we trigger it more faster.